Finding aid to the Christmas records CA.MS.00111
Smith College Archives
Christmas records
1900-1991
Smith College Archives
Smith College.
CA.MS.00111
0.625 linear feet (2 containers)
Since 1900, Christmas at Smith College has involved the sending of cards, the singing of carols, and the annual Vespers. Smith College's Christmas Vespers have allowed religious and non-religious students alike to come together and appreciate the music and spirit of the holiday season for over one hundred years. Materials include cards, programs, clippings, and photographs.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Source unknown
Biographical / Historical
Since 1900, Christmas at Smith College has involved the sending of cards, the singing of carols, and, of course, the annual Vespers. Smith College's Christmas Vespers have allowed religious and non-religious students alike to come together and appreciate the music and spirit of the holiday season for over one hundred years. At this annual candlelight ceremony, Smith College choral groups perform seasonal songs and religious readings.
Scope and Contents
Materials include cards, programs, clippings, and photographs.
Christmas--Massachusetts--Northampton.; Christmas cards--Massachusetts--Northampton.; Smith College--History--Sources.; Smith College--Students--Social life and customs.
- Calendar of Stations, 1942 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1912-1913 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1949 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1951 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1953 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1954 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1955 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1956 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1957 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1958 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1959 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1960 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1961 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1962 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1963 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1964 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1965 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1966 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Cards, 1967 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Vespers: Photographs, 1949-1970 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1900-1920 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1921-1940 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1941-1950 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1951-1960 (Box 3081)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1961-1970 (Box 3081)
- General, 1900-1970 (Box 3081)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1900-1935 (Box 3081)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1936-1950 (Box 3081)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1951-1970 (Box 3081)
- Photographs, 1914-1970 (Box 3081)
- "See Also", undated (Box 3081)
- Christmas Vepsers: Photographs, 1971 (Box 3082)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1971-1980 (Box 3082)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1981-1990 (Box 3082)
- Christmas Vespers: Programs, 1991 (Box 3082)
- Christmas Vespers, undated (Box 3082)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1971 (Box 3082)
- Photographs, 1971 (Box 3082)